{
  "frames": [
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "baker_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 0,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 840
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.82470703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.82080078125,
        "right": 0.82763671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "baker_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 1,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 904
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.88720703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.88330078125,
        "right": 0.89013671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "baker_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 2,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 896
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.87939453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.87548828125,
        "right": 0.88232421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "baker_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "baker_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 3,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 517,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51513671875,
        "bottom": 0.50537109375,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.52490234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "baker_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "baker_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 4,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 517,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51513671875,
        "bottom": 0.50537109375,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.52490234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "baker_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "baker_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 5,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 517,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51513671875,
        "bottom": 0.50537109375,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.52490234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "baker_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 6,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 96
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.09423828125,
        "right": 0.10888671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "baker_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 7,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 112
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.11767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.10986328125,
        "right": 0.12451171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "baker_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 8,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 128
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.13330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.12548828125,
        "right": 0.14013671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "baker_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 9,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 357
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.34912109375,
        "right": 0.36962890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "baker_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 10,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 389
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.38037109375,
        "right": 0.40087890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "baker_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "baker_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 11,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 197
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.19287109375,
        "right": 0.21337890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 12,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 888
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.87158203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.86767578125,
        "right": 0.87451171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 13,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 808
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.79345703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.78955078125,
        "right": 0.79638671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 14,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 800
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.78564453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.78173828125,
        "right": 0.78857421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 15,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 519,
        "left": 144
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51513671875,
        "bottom": 0.50732421875,
        "left": 0.14111328125,
        "right": 0.15576171875,
        "top": 0.52294921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 16,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 519,
        "left": 160
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.16455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51513671875,
        "bottom": 0.50732421875,
        "left": 0.15673828125,
        "right": 0.17138671875,
        "top": 0.52294921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 17,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 519,
        "left": 224
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.22705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51513671875,
        "bottom": 0.50732421875,
        "left": 0.21923828125,
        "right": 0.23388671875,
        "top": 0.52294921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 18,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 19,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 20,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 21,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 192,
        "left": 421
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18798828125,
        "left": 0.41162109375,
        "right": 0.43212890625,
        "top": 0.21826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 22,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 192,
        "left": 453
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18798828125,
        "left": 0.44287109375,
        "right": 0.46337890625,
        "top": 0.21826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_1_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_1_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 23,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 5
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.00537109375,
        "right": 0.02587890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 24,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 792
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.77783203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.77392578125,
        "right": 0.78076171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 25,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 712
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.69970703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.69580078125,
        "right": 0.70263671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 26,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 704
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.69189453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.68798828125,
        "right": 0.69482421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 27,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 32
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.03955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.03173828125,
        "right": 0.04638671875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 28,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 48
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.05517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.04736328125,
        "right": 0.06201171875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 29,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 64
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.06298828125,
        "right": 0.07763671875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 30,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 31,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 32,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 33,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 192,
        "left": 421
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18798828125,
        "left": 0.41162109375,
        "right": 0.43212890625,
        "top": 0.21826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 34,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 165
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.16162109375,
        "right": 0.18212890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_2_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_2_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 35,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 197
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.19287109375,
        "right": 0.21337890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 36,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 696
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.68408203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.68017578125,
        "right": 0.68701171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 37,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 640
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.62939453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.62548828125,
        "right": 0.63232421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 38,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 632
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.62158203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.61767578125,
        "right": 0.62451171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 39,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 96
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.09423828125,
        "right": 0.10888671875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 40,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 112
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.11767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.10986328125,
        "right": 0.12451171875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 41,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 128
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.13330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.12548828125,
        "right": 0.14013671875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 42,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 144
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.14111328125,
        "right": 0.15576171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 43,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 160
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.16455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.15673828125,
        "right": 0.17138671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 44,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 176
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.18017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.17236328125,
        "right": 0.18701171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 45,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 261
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.25537109375,
        "right": 0.27587890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 46,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 293
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.28662109375,
        "right": 0.30712890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "captain_3_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "captain_3_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 47,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 325
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.31787109375,
        "right": 0.33837890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 48,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 624
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.61376953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.60986328125,
        "right": 0.61669921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 49,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 544
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.53564453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.53173828125,
        "right": 0.53857421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 50,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 536
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.52783203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.52392578125,
        "right": 0.53076171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 51,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 192
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.19580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.18798828125,
        "right": 0.20263671875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 52,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 1008
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.99267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.98486328125,
        "right": 0.99951171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 53,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 208
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.21142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.20361328125,
        "right": 0.21826171875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 54,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 55,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 56,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 57,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 485
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.47412109375,
        "right": 0.49462890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 58,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 5
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.00537109375,
        "right": 0.02587890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "deckhand_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "deckhand_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 59,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 37
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.03662109375,
        "right": 0.05712890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 60,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 528
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.52001953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.51611328125,
        "right": 0.52294921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 61,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 344
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.34033203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.33642578125,
        "right": 0.34326171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 62,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 440
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.43408203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.43017578125,
        "right": 0.43701171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 63,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 144
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.14111328125,
        "right": 0.15576171875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 64,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 128
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.13330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.12548828125,
        "right": 0.14013671875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 65,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 160
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.16455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.15673828125,
        "right": 0.17138671875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 66,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 224
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.22705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.21923828125,
        "right": 0.23388671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 67,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 240
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.24267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.23486328125,
        "right": 0.24951171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 68,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 256
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.25830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.25048828125,
        "right": 0.26513671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 69,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 293
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.28662109375,
        "right": 0.30712890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 70,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 325
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.31787109375,
        "right": 0.33837890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "dummy_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "dummy_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 71,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 357
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.34912109375,
        "right": 0.36962890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 72,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 336
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.33251953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.32861328125,
        "right": 0.33544921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 73,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 288
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.28564453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.28173828125,
        "right": 0.28857421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 74,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 256
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.25439453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.25048828125,
        "right": 0.25732421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 75,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 272
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.27392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.26611328125,
        "right": 0.28076171875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 76,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 288
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.28955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.28173828125,
        "right": 0.29638671875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 77,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 423,
        "left": 304
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.30517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42138671875,
        "bottom": 0.41357421875,
        "left": 0.29736328125,
        "right": 0.31201171875,
        "top": 0.42919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 78,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 79,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 320
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.31298828125,
        "right": 0.32763671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 80,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 336
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.33642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.32861328125,
        "right": 0.34326171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 81,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 165
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.16162109375,
        "right": 0.18212890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 82,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 197
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.19287109375,
        "right": 0.21337890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "engineer_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "engineer_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 83,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 229
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.22412109375,
        "right": 0.24462890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 84,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 248
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.24658203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.24267578125,
        "right": 0.24951171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 85,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 240
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23876953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.23486328125,
        "right": 0.24169921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 86,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 992
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.97314453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.96923828125,
        "right": 0.97607421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 87,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 422,
        "left": 352
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.41259765625,
        "left": 0.34423828125,
        "right": 0.35888671875,
        "top": 0.43115234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.01953125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 88,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 422,
        "left": 368
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.36767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.41259765625,
        "left": 0.35986328125,
        "right": 0.37451171875,
        "top": 0.43115234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.01953125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 89,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 422,
        "left": 384
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.38330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.41259765625,
        "left": 0.37548828125,
        "right": 0.39013671875,
        "top": 0.43115234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.01953125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 90,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 400
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.39111328125,
        "right": 0.40576171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 91,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 416
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.41455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.40673828125,
        "right": 0.42138671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 92,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 432
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.43017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.42236328125,
        "right": 0.43701171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 93,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 137,
        "left": 131
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.13427734375,
        "left": 0.12841796875,
        "right": 0.15283203125,
        "top": 0.17822265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 94,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 137,
        "left": 163
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.13427734375,
        "left": 0.15966796875,
        "right": 0.18408203125,
        "top": 0.17822265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_1_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_1_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 95,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 137,
        "left": 195
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.13427734375,
        "left": 0.19091796875,
        "right": 0.21533203125,
        "top": 0.17822265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 96,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 984
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.96533203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.96142578125,
        "right": 0.96826171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 97,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 976
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.95751953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.95361328125,
        "right": 0.96044921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 98,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 848
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.83251953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.82861328125,
        "right": 0.83544921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 99,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 326,
        "left": 132
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31884765625,
        "left": 0.12939453125,
        "right": 0.15185546875,
        "top": 0.33740234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.01953125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 100,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 326,
        "left": 164
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31884765625,
        "left": 0.16064453125,
        "right": 0.18310546875,
        "top": 0.33740234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.01953125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 101,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 20,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 326,
        "left": 196
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31884765625,
        "left": 0.19189453125,
        "right": 0.21435546875,
        "top": 0.33740234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.01953125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 102,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 448
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.44580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.43798828125,
        "right": 0.45263671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 103,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 464
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.46142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.45361328125,
        "right": 0.46826171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 104,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 480
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.47705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.46923828125,
        "right": 0.48388671875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 105,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 136,
        "left": 229
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15576171875,
        "bottom": 0.13330078125,
        "left": 0.22412109375,
        "right": 0.24462890625,
        "top": 0.17822265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0458984375,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 106,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 136,
        "left": 261
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15576171875,
        "bottom": 0.13330078125,
        "left": 0.25537109375,
        "right": 0.27587890625,
        "top": 0.17822265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0458984375,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_2_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_2_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 107,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 136,
        "left": 293
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15576171875,
        "bottom": 0.13330078125,
        "left": 0.28662109375,
        "right": 0.30712890625,
        "top": 0.17822265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0458984375,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 108,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 784
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.77001953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.76611328125,
        "right": 0.77294921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 109,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 752
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.73876953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.73486328125,
        "right": 0.74169921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 110,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 744
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.73095703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.72705078125,
        "right": 0.73388671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 111,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 357,
        "left": 4
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35888671875,
        "bottom": 0.34912109375,
        "left": 0.00439453125,
        "right": 0.02685546875,
        "top": 0.36865234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 112,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 357,
        "left": 36
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35888671875,
        "bottom": 0.34912109375,
        "left": 0.03564453125,
        "right": 0.05810546875,
        "top": 0.36865234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 113,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 357,
        "left": 68
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35888671875,
        "bottom": 0.34912109375,
        "left": 0.06689453125,
        "right": 0.08935546875,
        "top": 0.36865234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 114,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 480
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.47705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.46923828125,
        "right": 0.48388671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 115,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 496
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.49267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.48486328125,
        "right": 0.49951171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 116,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 117,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 48,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 48,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 136,
        "left": 323
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.13330078125,
        "left": 0.31591796875,
        "right": 0.34033203125,
        "top": 0.17919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.046875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 118,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 48,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 48,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 136,
        "left": 355
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.13330078125,
        "left": 0.34716796875,
        "right": 0.37158203125,
        "top": 0.17919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.046875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_3_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_3_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 119,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 48,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 48,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 136,
        "left": 387
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.13330078125,
        "left": 0.37841796875,
        "right": 0.40283203125,
        "top": 0.17919921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.046875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 120,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 688
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.67626953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.67236328125,
        "right": 0.67919921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 121,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 656
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.64501953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.64111328125,
        "right": 0.64794921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 122,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 648
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.63720703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.63330078125,
        "right": 0.64013671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 123,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 357,
        "left": 388
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35888671875,
        "bottom": 0.34912109375,
        "left": 0.37939453125,
        "right": 0.40185546875,
        "top": 0.36865234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 124,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 357,
        "left": 420
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35888671875,
        "bottom": 0.34912109375,
        "left": 0.41064453125,
        "right": 0.43310546875,
        "top": 0.36865234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 12,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 125,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 24
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 357,
        "left": 452
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35888671875,
        "bottom": 0.34912109375,
        "left": 0.44189453125,
        "right": 0.46435546875,
        "top": 0.36865234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.0234375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 126,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 127,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 32
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.03955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.03173828125,
        "right": 0.04638671875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 128,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 48
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.05517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.04736328125,
        "right": 0.06201171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 129,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 136,
        "left": 419
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15576171875,
        "bottom": 0.13330078125,
        "left": 0.40966796875,
        "right": 0.43408203125,
        "top": 0.17822265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0458984375,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 130,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 72,
        "left": 227
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09326171875,
        "bottom": 0.07080078125,
        "left": 0.22216796875,
        "right": 0.24658203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0458984375,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 24
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_4_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_4_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 131,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 47,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 72,
        "left": 259
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09326171875,
        "bottom": 0.07080078125,
        "left": 0.25341796875,
        "right": 0.27783203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0458984375,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 132,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 616
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.60595703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.60205078125,
        "right": 0.60888671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 133,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 416
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.41064453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.40673828125,
        "right": 0.41357421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 134,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 408
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.40283203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.39892578125,
        "right": 0.40576171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 135,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 453,
        "left": 64
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44287109375,
        "left": 0.06298828125,
        "right": 0.07763671875,
        "top": 0.46240234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 136,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 453,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44287109375,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.46240234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 10
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 11
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 137,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 21,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 453,
        "left": 96
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44287109375,
        "left": 0.09423828125,
        "right": 0.10888671875,
        "top": 0.46240234375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0205078125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 138,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 112
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.11767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.10986328125,
        "right": 0.12451171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 139,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 128
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.13330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.12548828125,
        "right": 0.14013671875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 140,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 144
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.14111328125,
        "right": 0.15576171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 141,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 9,
        "left": 451
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.03173828125,
        "bottom": 0.00927734375,
        "left": 0.44091796875,
        "right": 0.46533203125,
        "top": 0.05322265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 142,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 419
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.40966796875,
        "right": 0.43408203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "female_civilian_passenger_5_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "female_civilian_passenger_5_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 143,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 451
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.44091796875,
        "right": 0.46533203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 17
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 17
        },
        "displayName": "barrel_1",
        "filenameStem": "barrel_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 144,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 32
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 32
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 143,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.14013671875,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.17236328125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.033203125,
        "width": 0.03125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 13
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 14
        },
        "displayName": "bed_1",
        "filenameStem": "bed_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 145,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 27,
          "width": 64
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 27,
          "width": 64
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 194,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.03173828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20263671875,
        "bottom": 0.18994140625,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.06201171875,
        "top": 0.21533203125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0263671875,
        "width": 0.0625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 13
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 14
        },
        "displayName": "bed_2",
        "filenameStem": "bed_2",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 146,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 27,
          "width": 64
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 27,
          "width": 64
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 194,
        "left": 64
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.09423828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20263671875,
        "bottom": 0.18994140625,
        "left": 0.06298828125,
        "right": 0.12451171875,
        "top": 0.21533203125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0263671875,
        "width": 0.0625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 28,
          "y": 20
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 28,
          "y": 20
        },
        "displayName": "cabin_desk_1",
        "filenameStem": "cabin_desk_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 147,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 40,
          "width": 56
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 40,
          "width": 56
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 12,
        "left": 388
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.40673828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.03173828125,
        "bottom": 0.01220703125,
        "left": 0.37939453125,
        "right": 0.43310546875,
        "top": 0.05029296875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0390625,
        "width": 0.0546875
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "chest_1",
        "filenameStem": "chest_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 148,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 37
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.03662109375,
        "right": 0.05712890625,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "chest_2",
        "filenameStem": "chest_2",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 149,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 5
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.00537109375,
        "right": 0.02587890625,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "chest_3",
        "filenameStem": "chest_3",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 150,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 69
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.06787109375,
        "right": 0.08837890625,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 23,
          "y": 14
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 23,
          "y": 15
        },
        "displayName": "coal_cart",
        "filenameStem": "coal_cart",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 151,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 29,
          "width": 46
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 29,
          "width": 46
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 193,
        "left": 137
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.15673828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20263671875,
        "bottom": 0.18896484375,
        "left": 0.13427734375,
        "right": 0.17822265625,
        "top": 0.21630859375
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0283203125,
        "width": 0.044921875
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "crate_1",
        "filenameStem": "crate_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 152,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 32
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 32
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 224
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.21923828125,
        "right": 0.24951171875,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.03125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 17
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 17
        },
        "displayName": "diesel_can_1",
        "filenameStem": "diesel_can_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 153,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 27
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 27
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 143,
        "left": 34
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04638671875,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15673828125,
        "bottom": 0.14013671875,
        "left": 0.03369140625,
        "right": 0.05908203125,
        "top": 0.17236328125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.033203125,
        "width": 0.0263671875
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 14,
          "y": 20
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 14,
          "y": 21
        },
        "displayName": "dining_chair_1",
        "filenameStem": "dining_chair_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 154,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 41,
          "width": 28
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 41,
          "width": 28
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 139,
        "left": 66
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15576171875,
        "bottom": 0.13623046875,
        "left": 0.06494140625,
        "right": 0.09130859375,
        "top": 0.17529296875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0400390625,
        "width": 0.02734375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 14,
          "y": 20
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 14,
          "y": 21
        },
        "displayName": "dining_chair_2",
        "filenameStem": "dining_chair_2",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 155,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 41,
          "width": 28
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 41,
          "width": 28
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 139,
        "left": 98
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.15576171875,
        "bottom": 0.13623046875,
        "left": 0.09619140625,
        "right": 0.12255859375,
        "top": 0.17529296875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0400390625,
        "width": 0.02734375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 17
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 17
        },
        "displayName": "drum_1",
        "filenameStem": "drum_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 156,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 79,
        "left": 131
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07763671875,
        "left": 0.12841796875,
        "right": 0.15283203125,
        "top": 0.10986328125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.033203125,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 17
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 17
        },
        "displayName": "drum_2",
        "filenameStem": "drum_2",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 157,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 79,
        "left": 387
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07763671875,
        "left": 0.37841796875,
        "right": 0.40283203125,
        "top": 0.10986328125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.033203125,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 41
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 41
        },
        "displayName": "hydrogen_tank_1",
        "filenameStem": "hydrogen_tank_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 158,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 82,
          "width": 33
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 82,
          "width": 33
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 23,
        "left": 15
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.03076171875,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.06298828125,
        "bottom": 0.02294921875,
        "left": 0.01513671875,
        "right": 0.04638671875,
        "top": 0.10205078125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.080078125,
        "width": 0.0322265625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 15
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 15
        },
        "displayName": "large_dining_table_1",
        "filenameStem": "large_dining_table_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 159,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 30,
          "width": 64
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 30,
          "width": 64
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 193,
        "left": 320
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.34423828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18896484375,
        "left": 0.31298828125,
        "right": 0.37451171875,
        "top": 0.21728515625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.029296875,
        "width": 0.0625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 15
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 32,
          "y": 15
        },
        "displayName": "large_dining_table_2",
        "filenameStem": "large_dining_table_2",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 160,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 30,
          "width": 64
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 30,
          "width": 64
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 193,
        "left": 256
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.28173828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18896484375,
        "left": 0.25048828125,
        "right": 0.31201171875,
        "top": 0.21728515625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.029296875,
        "width": 0.0625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "particle_1",
        "filenameStem": "particle_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 161,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 32
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 32
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 448
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.43798828125,
        "right": 0.46826171875,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.03125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 25,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 25,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "piano_1",
        "filenameStem": "piano_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 162,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 50
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 50
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 192,
        "left": 199
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.21923828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18798828125,
        "left": 0.19482421875,
        "right": 0.24267578125,
        "top": 0.21826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.048828125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 17,
          "y": 25
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 17,
          "y": 25
        },
        "displayName": "powder_keg_1",
        "filenameStem": "powder_keg_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 163,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 50,
          "width": 35
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 50,
          "width": 35
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 7,
        "left": 142
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.15576171875,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.03173828125,
        "bottom": 0.00732421875,
        "left": 0.13916015625,
        "right": 0.17236328125,
        "top": 0.05517578125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.048828125,
        "width": 0.0341796875
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 15
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 15
        },
        "displayName": "small_table_1",
        "filenameStem": "small_table_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 164,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 30,
          "width": 32
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 30,
          "width": 32
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 257,
        "left": 256
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25146484375,
        "left": 0.25048828125,
        "right": 0.28076171875,
        "top": 0.27978515625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.029296875,
        "width": 0.03125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 15
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "small_table_2",
        "filenameStem": "small_table_2",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 165,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 31,
          "width": 32
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 31,
          "width": 32
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 480
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26513671875,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.46923828125,
        "right": 0.49951171875,
        "top": 0.27978515625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0302734375,
        "width": 0.03125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 41
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 16,
          "y": 41
        },
        "displayName": "sodium_tank_1",
        "filenameStem": "sodium_tank_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 166,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 82,
          "width": 33
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 82,
          "width": 33
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 23,
        "left": 79
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.09326171875,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.06298828125,
        "bottom": 0.02294921875,
        "left": 0.07763671875,
        "right": 0.10888671875,
        "top": 0.10205078125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.080078125,
        "width": 0.0322265625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 29,
          "y": 21
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 29,
          "y": 21
        },
        "displayName": "stone_ballast_1",
        "filenameStem": "stone_ballast_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 167,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 42,
          "width": 58
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 42,
          "width": 58
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 11,
        "left": 323
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.34423828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.03173828125,
        "bottom": 0.01123046875,
        "left": 0.31591796875,
        "right": 0.37158203125,
        "top": 0.05126953125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.041015625,
        "width": 0.056640625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 17,
          "y": 17
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 17,
          "y": 17
        },
        "displayName": "tnt_crate_1",
        "filenameStem": "tnt_crate_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 168,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 34
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 34,
          "width": 34
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 15,
        "left": 271
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.28173828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.03173828125,
        "bottom": 0.01513671875,
        "left": 0.26513671875,
        "right": 0.29736328125,
        "top": 0.04736328125
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.033203125,
        "width": 0.033203125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 31,
          "y": 31
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 31,
          "y": 31
        },
        "displayName": "tungsten_block_1",
        "filenameStem": "tungsten_block_1",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 169,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 62,
          "width": 62
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 62,
          "width": 62
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 1,
        "left": 193
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.21923828125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.03173828125,
        "bottom": 0.00146484375,
        "left": 0.18896484375,
        "right": 0.24853515625,
        "top": 0.06103515625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.060546875,
        "width": 0.060546875
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 170,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 448
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.44189453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.43798828125,
        "right": 0.44482421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 171,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 432
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42626953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.42236328125,
        "right": 0.42919921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 172,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 968
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.94970703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.94580078125,
        "right": 0.95263671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 173,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 160
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.16455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.15673828125,
        "right": 0.17138671875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 174,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 176
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.18017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.17236328125,
        "right": 0.18701171875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 175,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 192
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.19580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.18798828125,
        "right": 0.20263671875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 176,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 208
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.21142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.20361328125,
        "right": 0.21826171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 177,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 224
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.22705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.21923828125,
        "right": 0.23388671875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 178,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 240
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.24267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.23486328125,
        "right": 0.24951171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 179,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 101
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.09912109375,
        "right": 0.11962890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 180,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 133
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.13037109375,
        "right": 0.15087890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_1_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_1_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 181,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 165
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.16162109375,
        "right": 0.18212890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 182,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 600
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.59033203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.58642578125,
        "right": 0.59326171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 183,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 592
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.58251953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.57861328125,
        "right": 0.58544921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 184,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 584
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.57470703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.57080078125,
        "right": 0.57763671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 185,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 256
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.25830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.25048828125,
        "right": 0.26513671875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 186,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 272
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.27392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.26611328125,
        "right": 0.28076171875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 187,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 288
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.28955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.28173828125,
        "right": 0.29638671875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 188,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 304
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.30517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.29736328125,
        "right": 0.31201171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 189,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 320
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.31298828125,
        "right": 0.32763671875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 190,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 336
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.33642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.32861328125,
        "right": 0.34326171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 191,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 389
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.38037109375,
        "right": 0.40087890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 192,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 421
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.41162109375,
        "right": 0.43212890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_2_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_2_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 193,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 453
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.44287109375,
        "right": 0.46337890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 194,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 936
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.91845703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.91455078125,
        "right": 0.92138671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 195,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 880
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.86376953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.85986328125,
        "right": 0.86669921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 196,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 776
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.76220703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.75830078125,
        "right": 0.76513671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 197,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 352
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.34423828125,
        "right": 0.35888671875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 198,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 368
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.36767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.35986328125,
        "right": 0.37451171875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 199,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 384
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.38330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.37548828125,
        "right": 0.39013671875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 200,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 400
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.39111328125,
        "right": 0.40576171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 201,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 416
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.41455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.40673828125,
        "right": 0.42138671875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 202,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 432
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.43017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.42236328125,
        "right": 0.43701171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 203,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 5
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.00537109375,
        "right": 0.02587890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 204,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 37
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.03662109375,
        "right": 0.05712890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_3_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_3_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 205,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 69
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.06787109375,
        "right": 0.08837890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 206,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 392
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.38720703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.38330078125,
        "right": 0.39013671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 207,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 384
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.37939453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.37548828125,
        "right": 0.38232421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 208,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 328
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32470703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.32080078125,
        "right": 0.32763671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 209,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 448
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.44580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.43798828125,
        "right": 0.45263671875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 210,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 455,
        "left": 464
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.46142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45263671875,
        "bottom": 0.44482421875,
        "left": 0.45361328125,
        "right": 0.46826171875,
        "top": 0.46044921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 211,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 368
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.36767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.35986328125,
        "right": 0.37451171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 212,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 448,
        "left": 496
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.49267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.45361328125,
        "bottom": 0.43798828125,
        "left": 0.48486328125,
        "right": 0.49951171875,
        "top": 0.46826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 213,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 214,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 215,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 133
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.13037109375,
        "right": 0.15087890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 216,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 101
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.09912109375,
        "right": 0.11962890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_4_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_4_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 217,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 325
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.31787109375,
        "right": 0.33837890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 218,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 400
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39501953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.39111328125,
        "right": 0.39794921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 219,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 520
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.51220703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.50830078125,
        "right": 0.51513671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 220,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 576
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.56689453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.56298828125,
        "right": 0.56982421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 221,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 32
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.03955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.03173828125,
        "right": 0.04638671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 222,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 48
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.05517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.04736328125,
        "right": 0.06201171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 223,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 64
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.06298828125,
        "right": 0.07763671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 224,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 225,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 96
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.09423828125,
        "right": 0.10888671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 226,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 112
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.11767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.10986328125,
        "right": 0.12451171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 227,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 261
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.25537109375,
        "right": 0.27587890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 228,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 229
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.22412109375,
        "right": 0.24462890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_5_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_5_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 229,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 485
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.47412109375,
        "right": 0.49462890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 230,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 944
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.92626953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.92236328125,
        "right": 0.92919921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 231,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 952
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.93408203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.93017578125,
        "right": 0.93701171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 232,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 960
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.94189453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.93798828125,
        "right": 0.94482421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 233,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 128
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.13330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.12548828125,
        "right": 0.14013671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 234,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 144
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.14111328125,
        "right": 0.15576171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 235,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 160
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.16455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.15673828125,
        "right": 0.17138671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 236,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 176
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.18017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.17236328125,
        "right": 0.18701171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 237,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 192
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.19580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.18798828125,
        "right": 0.20263671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 238,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 208
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.21142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.20361328125,
        "right": 0.21826171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 239,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 37
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.03662109375,
        "right": 0.05712890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 240,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 5
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.00537109375,
        "right": 0.02587890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_civ_6_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_civ_6_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 241,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 485
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.47412109375,
        "right": 0.49462890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 242,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 608
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.59814453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.59423828125,
        "right": 0.60107421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 243,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 760
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.74658203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.74267578125,
        "right": 0.74951171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 244,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 768
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.75439453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.75048828125,
        "right": 0.75732421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 245,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 224
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.22705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.21923828125,
        "right": 0.23388671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 246,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 240
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.24267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.23486328125,
        "right": 0.24951171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 247,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 256
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.25830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.25048828125,
        "right": 0.26513671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 248,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 272
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.27392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.26611328125,
        "right": 0.28076171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 249,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 288
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.28955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.28173828125,
        "right": 0.29638671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 250,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 304
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.30517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.29736328125,
        "right": 0.31201171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 251,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 357
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.34912109375,
        "right": 0.36962890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 252,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 325
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.31787109375,
        "right": 0.33837890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_1_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_1_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 253,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 133
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.13037109375,
        "right": 0.15087890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 254,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 480
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.47314453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.46923828125,
        "right": 0.47607421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 255,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 488
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48095703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.47705078125,
        "right": 0.48388671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 256,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 496
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48876953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.48486328125,
        "right": 0.49169921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 11
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 12
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 257,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 228,
        "left": 135
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23388671875,
        "bottom": 0.22314453125,
        "left": 0.13232421875,
        "right": 0.14892578125,
        "top": 0.24462890625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0224609375,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 11
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 12
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 258,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 228,
        "left": 103
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23388671875,
        "bottom": 0.22314453125,
        "left": 0.10107421875,
        "right": 0.11767578125,
        "top": 0.24462890625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0224609375,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 11
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 12
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 259,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 228,
        "left": 71
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23388671875,
        "bottom": 0.22314453125,
        "left": 0.06982421875,
        "right": 0.08642578125,
        "top": 0.24462890625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0224609375,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 260,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 320
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.31298828125,
        "right": 0.32763671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 261,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 336
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.33642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.32861328125,
        "right": 0.34326171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 262,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 352
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.34423828125,
        "right": 0.35888671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 263,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 421
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.41162109375,
        "right": 0.43212890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 264,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 101
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.09912109375,
        "right": 0.11962890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "male_wealthy_passenger_2_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 265,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 69
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.06787109375,
        "right": 0.08837890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 266,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 424
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.41845703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.41455078125,
        "right": 0.42138671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 267,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 504
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.49658203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.49267578125,
        "right": 0.49951171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 268,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 512
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.50439453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.50048828125,
        "right": 0.50732421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 269,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 384
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.38330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.37548828125,
        "right": 0.39013671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 270,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 400
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.39111328125,
        "right": 0.40576171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 271,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 416
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.41455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.40673828125,
        "right": 0.42138671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 272,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 320
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.31298828125,
        "right": 0.32763671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 273,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 336
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.33642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.32861328125,
        "right": 0.34326171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 274,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 352
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.34423828125,
        "right": 0.35888671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 275,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 192,
        "left": 389
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18798828125,
        "left": 0.38037109375,
        "right": 0.40087890625,
        "top": 0.21826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 276,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 357
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.34912109375,
        "right": 0.36962890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_3_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_3_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 277,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 325
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.31787109375,
        "right": 0.33837890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 278,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 664
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.65283203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.64892578125,
        "right": 0.65576171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 279,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 672
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.66064453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.65673828125,
        "right": 0.66357421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 280,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 680
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.66845703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.66455078125,
        "right": 0.67138671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 11
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 12
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 281,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 356,
        "left": 295
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35888671875,
        "bottom": 0.34814453125,
        "left": 0.28857421875,
        "right": 0.30517578125,
        "top": 0.36962890625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0224609375,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 11
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 12
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 282,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 324,
        "left": 487
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32763671875,
        "bottom": 0.31689453125,
        "left": 0.47607421875,
        "right": 0.49267578125,
        "top": 0.33837890625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0224609375,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 11
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 12
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 283,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 23,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 324,
        "left": 455
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32763671875,
        "bottom": 0.31689453125,
        "left": 0.44482421875,
        "right": 0.46142578125,
        "top": 0.33837890625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0224609375,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 284,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 432
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.43017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.42236328125,
        "right": 0.43701171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 285,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 448
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.44580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.43798828125,
        "right": 0.45263671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 286,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 464
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.46142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.45361328125,
        "right": 0.46826171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 287,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 421
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.41162109375,
        "right": 0.43212890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 288,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 293
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.28662109375,
        "right": 0.30712890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "wealthy_passenger_4_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "wealthy_passenger_4_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 289,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 320,
        "left": 101
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.32861328125,
        "bottom": 0.31298828125,
        "left": 0.09912109375,
        "right": 0.11962890625,
        "top": 0.34326171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "officer_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 290,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 856
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.84033203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.83642578125,
        "right": 0.84326171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "officer_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 291,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 864
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.84814453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.84423828125,
        "right": 0.85107421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "officer_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 292,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 872
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.85595703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.85205078125,
        "right": 0.85888671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "officer_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "officer_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 293,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 480
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.47705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.46923828125,
        "right": 0.48388671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "officer_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "officer_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 294,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 496
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.49267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.48486328125,
        "right": 0.49951171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "officer_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "officer_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 295,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 512
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.50830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.50048828125,
        "right": 0.51513671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "officer_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 296,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "officer_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 297,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "officer_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 298,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "officer_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 299,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 192,
        "left": 421
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.20361328125,
        "bottom": 0.18798828125,
        "left": 0.41162109375,
        "right": 0.43212890625,
        "top": 0.21826171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "officer_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 300,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 197
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.19287109375,
        "right": 0.21337890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "officer_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "officer_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 301,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 5
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.00537109375,
        "right": 0.02587890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 302,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 1000
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.98095703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.97705078125,
        "right": 0.98388671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 303,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 320
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.31689453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.31298828125,
        "right": 0.31982421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 304,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 352
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.34814453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.34423828125,
        "right": 0.35107421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 305,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 528
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.52392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.51611328125,
        "right": 0.53076171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 306,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 544
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.53955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.53173828125,
        "right": 0.54638671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 307,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 560
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.55517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.54736328125,
        "right": 0.56201171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 308,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 576
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.57080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.56298828125,
        "right": 0.57763671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 309,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 592
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.58642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.57861328125,
        "right": 0.59326171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 310,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 608
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.60205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.59423828125,
        "right": 0.60888671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 311,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 293
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.28662109375,
        "right": 0.30712890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 312,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 261
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.25537109375,
        "right": 0.27587890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "oiler_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "oiler_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 313,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 453
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.44287109375,
        "right": 0.46337890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 314,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 264
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26220703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.25830078125,
        "right": 0.26513671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 315,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 272
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.27001953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.26611328125,
        "right": 0.27294921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 316,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 280
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.27783203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.27392578125,
        "right": 0.28076171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 317,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 224
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.22705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.21923828125,
        "right": 0.23388671875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 318,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 96
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.09423828125,
        "right": 0.10888671875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 319,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 112
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.11767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.10986328125,
        "right": 0.12451171875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 320,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 80
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.08642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.07861328125,
        "right": 0.09326171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 321,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 0
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.00830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.00048828125,
        "right": 0.01513671875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 322,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 416,
        "left": 16
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.02392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.42236328125,
        "bottom": 0.40673828125,
        "left": 0.01611328125,
        "right": 0.03076171875,
        "top": 0.43701171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 323,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 389
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.38037109375,
        "right": 0.40087890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 324,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 229
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.22412109375,
        "right": 0.24462890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "quartermaster_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "quartermaster_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 325,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 197
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.19287109375,
        "right": 0.21337890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 326,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 360
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35595703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.35205078125,
        "right": 0.35888671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 327,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 368
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.36376953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.35986328125,
        "right": 0.36669921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 328,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 376
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.37158203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.36767578125,
        "right": 0.37451171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 329,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 624
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.61767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.60986328125,
        "right": 0.62451171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 330,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 640
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.63330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.62548828125,
        "right": 0.64013671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 331,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 656
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.64892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.64111328125,
        "right": 0.65576171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 332,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 672
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.66455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.65673828125,
        "right": 0.67138671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 333,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 688
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.68017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.67236328125,
        "right": 0.68701171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 334,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 704
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.69580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.68798828125,
        "right": 0.70263671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 335,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 165
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.16162109375,
        "right": 0.18212890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 336,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 133
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.14111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.13037109375,
        "right": 0.15087890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_1_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_1_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 337,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 101
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.10986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.09912109375,
        "right": 0.11962890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 338,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 456
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.44970703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.44580078125,
        "right": 0.45263671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 339,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 464
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45751953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.45361328125,
        "right": 0.46044921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 340,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 472
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.46533203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.46142578125,
        "right": 0.46826171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 341,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 176
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.18017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.17236328125,
        "right": 0.18701171875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 342,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 192
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.19580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.18798828125,
        "right": 0.20263671875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 343,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 16,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 544,
        "left": 208
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.21142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.53955078125,
        "bottom": 0.53173828125,
        "left": 0.20361328125,
        "right": 0.21826171875,
        "top": 0.54638671875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 344,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 672
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.66455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.65673828125,
        "right": 0.67138671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 345,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 688
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.68017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.67236328125,
        "right": 0.68701171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 346,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 704
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.69580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.68798828125,
        "right": 0.70263671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 347,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 69
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.06787109375,
        "right": 0.08837890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 348,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 389
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.38037109375,
        "right": 0.40087890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "steward_2_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "steward_2_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 349,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 357
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.34912109375,
        "right": 0.36962890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 350,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 552
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.54345703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.53955078125,
        "right": 0.54638671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 351,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 560
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.55126953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.54736328125,
        "right": 0.55419921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 352,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 568
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.55908203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.55517578125,
        "right": 0.56201171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 353,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 720
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.71142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.70361328125,
        "right": 0.71826171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 354,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 736
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.72705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.71923828125,
        "right": 0.73388671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 355,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 752
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.74267578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.73486328125,
        "right": 0.74951171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 356,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 672
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.66455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.65673828125,
        "right": 0.67138671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 357,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 688
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.68017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.67236328125,
        "right": 0.68701171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 358,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 704
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.69580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.68798828125,
        "right": 0.70263671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 359,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 291
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.28466796875,
        "right": 0.30908203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 360,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 355
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.34716796875,
        "right": 0.37158203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_1_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_1_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 361,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 323
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.31591796875,
        "right": 0.34033203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 362,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 552
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.54345703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.53955078125,
        "right": 0.54638671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 363,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 560
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.55126953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.54736328125,
        "right": 0.55419921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 364,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 568
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.55908203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.55517578125,
        "right": 0.56201171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 365,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 768
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.75830078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.75048828125,
        "right": 0.76513671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 366,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 784
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.77392578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.76611328125,
        "right": 0.78076171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 367,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 800
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.78955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.78173828125,
        "right": 0.79638671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 368,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 672
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.66455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.65673828125,
        "right": 0.67138671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 369,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 688
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.68017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.67236328125,
        "right": 0.68701171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 370,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 704
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.69580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.68798828125,
        "right": 0.70263671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 371,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 291
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.28466796875,
        "right": 0.30908203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 372,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 195
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.19091796875,
        "right": 0.21533203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 13,
          "y": 23
        },
        "displayName": "stewardess_2_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "stewardess_2_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 373,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 46,
          "width": 26
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 73,
        "left": 163
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.09423828125,
        "bottom": 0.07177734375,
        "left": 0.15966796875,
        "right": 0.18408203125,
        "top": 0.11572265625
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.044921875,
        "width": 0.025390625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 374,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 720
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.70751953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.70361328125,
        "right": 0.71044921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 375,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 728
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.71533203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.71142578125,
        "right": 0.71826171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 376,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 736
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.72314453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.71923828125,
        "right": 0.72607421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 377,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 816
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.80517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.79736328125,
        "right": 0.81201171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 378,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 832
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.82080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.81298828125,
        "right": 0.82763671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 379,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 848
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.83642578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.82861328125,
        "right": 0.84326171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 380,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 864
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.85205078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.84423828125,
        "right": 0.85888671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 381,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 880
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.86767578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.85986328125,
        "right": 0.87451171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 382,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 896
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.88330078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.87548828125,
        "right": 0.89013671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 383,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 224,
        "left": 37
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.23486328125,
        "bottom": 0.21923828125,
        "left": 0.03662109375,
        "right": 0.05712890625,
        "top": 0.24951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 384,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 69
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.06787109375,
        "right": 0.08837890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_1_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_1_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 385,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 261
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.25537109375,
        "right": 0.27587890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 386,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 816
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.80126953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.79736328125,
        "right": 0.80419921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 387,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 824
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.80908203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.80517578125,
        "right": 0.81201171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 388,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 832
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.81689453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.81298828125,
        "right": 0.81982421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 389,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 912
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.89892578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.89111328125,
        "right": 0.90576171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 390,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 928
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.91455078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.90673828125,
        "right": 0.92138671875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 391,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 487,
        "left": 944
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.93017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48388671875,
        "bottom": 0.47607421875,
        "left": 0.92236328125,
        "right": 0.93701171875,
        "top": 0.49169921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 392,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 960
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.94580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.93798828125,
        "right": 0.95263671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 393,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 976
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.96142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.95361328125,
        "right": 0.96826171875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 394,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 480,
        "left": 992
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.97705078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.48486328125,
        "bottom": 0.46923828125,
        "left": 0.96923828125,
        "right": 0.98388671875,
        "top": 0.49951171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 395,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 352,
        "left": 229
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.35986328125,
        "bottom": 0.34423828125,
        "left": 0.22412109375,
        "right": 0.24462890625,
        "top": 0.37451171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 396,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 37
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.04736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.03662109375,
        "right": 0.05712890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_2_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_2_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 397,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 288,
        "left": 5
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.01611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.29736328125,
        "bottom": 0.28173828125,
        "left": 0.00537109375,
        "right": 0.02587890625,
        "top": 0.31201171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 398,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 912
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.89501953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.89111328125,
        "right": 0.89794921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 399,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 920
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.90283203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.89892578125,
        "right": 0.90576171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 400,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 928
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.91064453125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.90673828125,
        "right": 0.91357421875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 401,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 391,
        "left": 167
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.17236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39013671875,
        "bottom": 0.38232421875,
        "left": 0.16357421875,
        "right": 0.18017578125,
        "top": 0.39794921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 402,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 391,
        "left": 199
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.20361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39013671875,
        "bottom": 0.38232421875,
        "left": 0.19482421875,
        "right": 0.21142578125,
        "top": 0.39794921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 403,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 391,
        "left": 231
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.23486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39013671875,
        "bottom": 0.38232421875,
        "left": 0.22607421875,
        "right": 0.24267578125,
        "top": 0.39794921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 404,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 32
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.03955078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.03173828125,
        "right": 0.04638671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 405,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 48
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.05517578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.04736328125,
        "right": 0.06201171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 406,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 64
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.07080078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.06298828125,
        "right": 0.07763671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 407,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 261
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.26611328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.25537109375,
        "right": 0.27587890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 408,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 293
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29736328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.28662109375,
        "right": 0.30712890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_3_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_3_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 409,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 325
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.32861328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.31787109375,
        "right": 0.33837890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_arm_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_arm_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 410,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 296
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.29345703125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.28955078125,
        "right": 0.29638671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_arm_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_arm_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 411,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 304
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.30126953125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.29736328125,
        "right": 0.30419921875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 4,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_arm_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_arm_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 412,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 8
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 312
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.30908203125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.30517578125,
        "right": 0.31201171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.0078125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_head_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_head_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 413,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 391,
        "left": 359
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.35986328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39013671875,
        "bottom": 0.38232421875,
        "left": 0.35107421875,
        "right": 0.36767578125,
        "top": 0.39794921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_head_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_head_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 414,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 391,
        "left": 391
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.39111328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39013671875,
        "bottom": 0.38232421875,
        "left": 0.38232421875,
        "right": 0.39892578125,
        "top": 0.39794921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 8
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 9,
          "y": 9
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_head_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_head_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 415,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 17,
          "width": 18
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 391,
        "left": 423
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39013671875,
        "bottom": 0.38232421875,
        "left": 0.41357421875,
        "right": 0.43017578125,
        "top": 0.39794921875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.0166015625,
        "width": 0.017578125
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_leg_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_leg_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 416,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 176
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.18017578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.17236328125,
        "right": 0.18701171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_leg_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_leg_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 417,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 192
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.19580078125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.18798828125,
        "right": 0.20263671875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 8,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_leg_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_leg_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 418,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 16
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 512,
        "left": 208
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.21142578125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.51611328125,
        "bottom": 0.50048828125,
        "left": 0.20361328125,
        "right": 0.21826171875,
        "top": 0.53076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.015625
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_torso_back",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_torso_back",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 419,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 453
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.45361328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.44287109375,
        "right": 0.46337890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_torso_front",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_torso_front",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 420,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 384,
        "left": 485
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.48486328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.39111328125,
        "bottom": 0.37548828125,
        "left": 0.47412109375,
        "right": 0.49462890625,
        "top": 0.40576171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    },
    {
      "frame": {
        "anchor_center": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "anchor_center_world": {
          "x": 11,
          "y": 16
        },
        "displayName": "stoker_4_torso_side",
        "filenameStem": "stoker_4_torso_side",
        "has_own_ambient_light": false,
        "id": {
          "frameIndex": 421,
          "group": 0
        },
        "size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        },
        "world_size": {
          "height": 32,
          "width": 22
        }
      },
      "frame_coordinates": {
        "bottom": 256,
        "left": 421
      },
      "texture_coordinates": {
        "anchorCenterX": 0.42236328125,
        "anchorCenterY": 0.26611328125,
        "bottom": 0.25048828125,
        "left": 0.41162109375,
        "right": 0.43212890625,
        "top": 0.28076171875
      },
      "texture_space_size": {
        "height": 0.03125,
        "width": 0.021484375
      }
    }
  ],
  "options": 14,
  "size": {
    "height": 1024,
    "width": 1024
  }
}
